Vodka, extremely versatile liquor, but, what's the best drink to have it with?
Hi, my name's Jeff Klein, and I'm a vodka connoisseur and bartender, here at Beak's Old Florida, St. Petersburg.
And I'm going to tell you what's the best tasting vodka drink.
Now, I think you should stick with the classics.
And that is a martini.
But, nothing compliments a vodka martini better than olive juice.
So, the best tasting vodka drink would be a dirty martini.
Now, the trick is, you don't want to put in too much olive juice, cause, if you wanted that you would just be drinking the olive juice.
Second, you get yourself a good vodka, over ice, a good shake to it, and a martini glass.
All fairly simple so far.
Mixes up with a nice little off color to it, let's you know that olive juice is in there, put a couple olives on a sword, and ready to serve.
It's a classic, never go wrong.
Olive juice compliments the vodka perfectly, and almost anybody will love it.
So, that is your best tasting vodka drink.
My name's Jeff Klein and I'm vodka connoisseur and bartender here at Beak's Old Florida, St. Pete.